# Finn Mitchell-Anyon

5

# Composer / Sound Designer / Audio Programmer

finn.mitchellanyon@gmail.com

0278220405

https://finneganeganegan.xyz/

Wellington NZ, 6021

# Summary

Composer and sound designer for games and media. Experienced with producing music and sound effects in a variety of styles, as well as integrating audio using game engines and audio middleware. Passionate about exploring the intersection between visuals and sound.

#### Education

- Bachelor of Design Innovation in Media Design,
  Victoria University of Wellington, 2016-2018
- **Postgraduate Diploma in Composition/Sonic Arts** (Graduated with Distinction) Victoria University of Wellington, 2019

# Certifications and Achievements

- Grade 8 Performance Piano, NZMEB, awarded with distinction
- Grade 5 Music Theory, NZMEB, awarded with distinction
- Outstanding Young Participant Award, Regenerate Game Jam Matariki 2022

# Experience

#### Game composer

Freelance, 2019 - Present

- Composed original music and sound effects for games
- Collaborated with the developers to find the right sonic direction for their game
- Managed my time to produce audio assets by the given deadline

#### Piano teacher

Wellington Music Academy, 2017 - Present

• Taught students how to read and perform music on the piano

## Skills

#### **S**oftware

- Unity
- Unreal
- FMOD
- WWise
- Ableton Live
- Pro Tools
- Reaper

#### **Programming**

- Javascript
- C#

#### Audio

- Recording
- Arrangement
- Mixing
- Mastering
- Synthesis

#### **Personal**

- Great Communicator
- Friendly and Cooperative
- Self-Managed
- Detail-Oriented

# Selected Projects

#### **Trigger Witch**

A NZ-made twin-stick shooter set in a fantasy world. The soundtrack I wrote dynamically reacts when the player enters combat, transitioning from a 16-bit orchestral style to a synth-metal rearrangement.

#### **Reorientation**

Week

A prototype for a first-person puzzle-platformer about reorienting gravity. I worked on music, sound design, and audio integration. The music becomes increasingly layered as the player redirects gravity.

#### **Voxelarium**

A procedurally generated sandbox which the player is able to freely explore and reshape. I designed the game's sound effects and implemented them using FMOD and C#.

### **Equine**

A horse racing and management game which I composed the soundtrack for. I wrote unique character themes for each of the game's playable characters, as well as the main theme.

#### **Forest**

An interactive audiovisual experience which I created with Javascript. The user plants musical trees to create a unique soundscape.